Christian Meyers

Hardworking, dedicated team player with IT Experience

Jackson, WI 53037 meyerscw0@gmail.com +1 262 305 2799

Professional Summary

Young and ambitious personality with four years in the restaurant industry, nine months in an IT Intern position, and current data center security and maintenance technician. Quick learner and always excited to understand new systems. Known to put in extra work to reach goals and provide excellent customer service and thoughtful contributions to current projects. Interest in cybersecurity and data protection. Always looking to improve team motivation and cohesion. Studying at U.W. Milwaukee and QUT Australia.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

TekSystems Contractor

TEKsystems-Menomonee Falls, WI July 2024 to Present

Currently contracting for a multi-billion dollar company overseeing and maintaining critical data center infrastructure during peak operation hours and ensuring a swift and minimally disruptive response in the event of any disaster.

Brand Ambassador-School of Information Studies

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Milwaukee, WI September 2023 to Present

Working with UWM Marketing and Communications and the School of Information Studies to represent the school and its values. Meeting with prospective and current students to tell them about the programs offered and appearing in promotional materials for the school.

Information Technology Intern

J.W. Speaker Corporation-Germantown, WI June 2023 to February 2024

IT intern associate focused on network and hardware systems. Working with outside vendors to secure and update our backend systems as well as upgrade the current data security measures.

Server/Bartender/Manager

Texas Roadhouse-West Bend, WI July 2019 to June 2023

Worked as Host, Busser, Togo Host, Waiter, and Bartender. Took over roles in management such as payroll and inventory administration, and assistant marketing lead for the store.

Education

Certificate in Cybersecurity

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee - Milwaukee, WI April 2023 to Present

Bachelor's degree in Information Science

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee - Milwaukee, WI September 2021 to Present

Semester Abroad in Information Security

QUT - Brisbane QLD

February 2024 to June 2024

Skills

- Serving
- · Microsoft Office
- · Direct sales
- User Experience (UX)
- Cybersecurity
- Application Development
- · Customer service
- Active Directory
- Information Security
- User Interface (UI)
- Bartending
- Restaurant experience
- Java
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft SQL Server
- Databases
- Python

Languages

- English Fluent
- German Intermediate

Additional Information

Recently switched field of study from marketing and business to Information technology.

Relevant coursework: Web Design 1, Intro to Information Studies, Intro to Computer Programming, Human Factors in Information Use, Intro to Application Development, Data Analysis and Visualisation, Database Information/Retrieval Systems, Building IT Systems, IT Systems Design, Information Security 1, Special IT Project Teams, Data Organisation Strategies

Upcoming relevant coursework: